Rahul Edathil

UIUX / Product Designer





I'm a UI/UX Product designer from Kochi, India with over 6+ years of experience. I specialize in designing and growing digital products, having worked on various projects in areas like Healthcare, E-commerce, Survey Tool. My focus is always on creating a great user experience, aligning with business objectives, and developing effective product strategies.

Work Experience



Cliniqon / Senior UI / UX Designer

Aug 2024 - Present

- Revamping The Current Website
- Taking responsibility for design requirements and ensuring their finalization



SurveySparrow / Visual Designer

Jun 2021 - Aug 2024

- New features are adding and old screens are redesigned according to the new design system
- Create design systems and pattern libraries to make sure our designs are consistent and work efficiently.
- Revamped the SurveySparrow Web app from top to bottom, enhancing UX, and paving the way for business growth.



Cabot Technologies UI/UX Designer

Jul 2019 - Jun 2021

- Collaborated with cross-functional teams to design and develop innovative products that met user needs and business goals
- Designed mobile and web-based applications
- Collaborated with Different Clients



2Base Technology / UI/UX Designer

Aug 2018- Jul 2019

- Conceptualised, designed complex projects, collaborating with renowned clients.



Fliptango Global Solutions / UI Developer

Mar 2017 - Apr 2018

- Write clean, efficient, and maintainable code using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript
- Developed responsive e-commerce websites using HTML, CSS

Education

Arena Animation

Diploma in Web and Graphic Designing

Chetana Media Institute

Non-Linear Editing

NIFE

Diploma In Fire and Safety Engineering

Higher Secondary

Commerce

Skills

Design

- UX Design UI Design
- Interaction Design Micro interactions
- Design System
 Service Design
- Typography Wireframing
- Color Theory
- Prototyping

Research

- Data Analysis User Interviews
- Journey mapping Usability Test
- Heuristics analysis
- Market Research
- User research A/B testing

Portfolio



Tools















